import React from 'react'
let  mythical = {
    title: "Mythical Creatures",
    questions: [
        {
            question: "This monster had 9 heads",
            answers: ["Cerberus", "Hydra", "Chiron", "Chimera"],
            correct: "Hydra"
        },
        {
            question: "This giant only had one eye",
            answers: ["Titan", "Arae", "Cyclops", "Pallas"],
            correct: "Cyclops"
        },
        {
            question: "This monster had 100 eyes",
            answers: [ "Satyr", "Argus", "Hippalectryon", "Cetus"],
            correct: "Argus"
        },
        {
            question: "The god Pan is portrayed as one of these",
            answers: ["Satyr", "Titan", "Centaur", "Athos"],
            correct: "Satyr"
        },
        {
            question: "This monster was the son of Zeus and lived in the labyrinth",
            answers: ["Cerberus", "Chiron", "Chimera","Minotaur"],
            correct: "Minotaur"
        },
        {
            question: "This monster loved riddles. And if you answered wrong, it would kill you.",
            answers: ["Sphynx", "Cetus", "Hydra", "Ipotane"],
            correct: "Sphynx"
        },
        {
            question: "This monster could literally sing you to death",
            answers: ["Typhon", "Siren", "Taraxippi", "Griffin"],
            correct: "Siren"
        },
        {
            question: "This monster was half woman and half bird",
            answers: ["Harpy", "Siren", "Gorgon", "Graeae"],
            correct: "Harpy"
        },
        {
            question: "This monster had the head of a lion, the body of a goat, and the tail of a serpent",
            answers: ["Cerberus", "Hippalectryon", "Laestrygonian", "Chimera"],
            correct: "Chimera"
        },
        {
            question: "This monster created a whirlpool to sink ships",
            answers: ["Charybdis", "Scylla", "Thoon", "Gigantes"],
            correct: "Charybdis"
        }
    ]
}

export default mythical